Megan Rodgers



FASHION DESIGN

(330) 354-8647

ⓒ

Canton, OH



www.meganrodgers.me



meganrodgers.me@gmail.com



EDUCATION

FASHION DESIGN

Minor: Sustainability Kent State University 2017 - 2020

SUSTAINABLE DESIGN ENTREPRENEUR

F.I.T - Continued Education 2016 - 2017

FASHION MERCHANDISING

Minor: Marketing Kent State University 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE
MACHINE KNITTING
DIGITAL KNITTING
TEXTILE DESIGN
MS OFFICE
BLUECHERRY - PLM SYSTEM

PROFILE

My name is Megan Kodgers and I am currently studying at Kent State University for Fashion Design and have a bachelor's degree in Fashion Merchandising. I was chosen as one of the top 30 students in my Senior class to be shown in the annual Portfolio Showcase. With my education and experience, I would be an assest to your company in Assistant Designer position. As a Design Assistant at Ellery Homestyles, I was described as having an "insane work ethic". I demonstrated that I had an eye for design and could be trusted to finish the job.

EXPERIENCES

DESIGN INTERN - SWEATER DEPARTMENT

Ann Taylor / New York, NY / June 2019 - Aug. 2019

- Spearheaded the design of a capsule collection for a Ann Taylor Intern presentation to high-level executives at the end of the internship
- Collaborated with Ann Taylor interns to target new customers
- Created Fall 2020 techpacks for Sweater Creative Design team
- Assisted in fit meetings, sketch reviews and Spring '20 P.O.V review
- Organized the Spring and Fall 2020 concept and line boards for sweater design team $\,$

DESIGN INTERN - BEDDING DEPARTMENT

Ellery Homestyles / New York, NY / June 2015 - Aug. 2015

- Assembled presentation boards and pulled fabric samples for buyer meetings
- Created and prepared engravings, mappings and pre-techs for Waverly, VUE, Historic Charleston, Belk and Blissliving collections to send overseas for production
- Controlled the design and production of nine pillows for the Jilo bedding collection for Belk
- Certified on the company's PLM System, Blue Cherry

DESIGN INTERN - BEDDING DEPARTMENT

Ellery Homestyles / New York, NY / June 2015 - Aug. 2015

- Assembled presentation boards and pulled fabric samples for buyer meetings
- Created and prepared engravings, mappings and pre-techs for Waverly, VUE, Historic Charleston, Belk and Blissliving collections to send overseas for production
- Controlled the design and production of nine pillows for the Jilo bedding collection for Belk